<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Nickwasused</title><link>https://nickwasused.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Nickwasused</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 19:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nickwasused.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to fix the PS4 Time after replacing the CMOS Battery on Firmware version 9.0?</title><link>https://nickwasused.com/posts/2022-03-27-ps4-time-wrong-after-cmos-change-900/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nickwasused.com/posts/2022-03-27-ps4-time-wrong-after-cmos-change-900/</guid><description>The Problem After I replaced the CMOS Battery on my Base Model PS4, I noticed that it couldn&amp;rsquo;t keep the time after a power loss. The PS4 is on firmware Version 9.0 where the CMOS Time Bomb was fixed. I mean it was fixed but e.g. Grand Theft Auto V (Version 1.38) with the No Intro were not able to start correctly (stuck at 90% Loading and heavy flickering).
The Fix The fix is very simple, but a little scary to do on a Jailbroken PS4.</description></item><item><title>How to install 32-bit BOINC on my 64-bit Raspberry Pi?</title><link>https://nickwasused.com/posts/2022-03-16-boinc-32bit-on-64bit-pi-dietpi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nickwasused.com/posts/2022-03-16-boinc-32bit-on-64bit-pi-dietpi/</guid><description>Why would you do this? Projects like UNIVERSE@HOME have no aarch64 Tasks. A Raspberry Pi 3b can´t run ROSETTA@HOME because it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have enough ram. DietPi, a popular OS for the raspberry pi, uses 64Bit. Requirements 64-bit raspberry pi e.g. DietPi Type uname -a the output should contain the following: aarch64 if there is armhf in the output then you can skip to the [Install](#Install 32-bit Boinc) section. Example output: Linux raspberrypi-1 5.</description></item><item><title>How do I block all the Twitter advertisers I've seen?</title><link>https://nickwasused.com/posts/2022-03-15-twitter-block-advertisers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 17:30:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nickwasused.com/posts/2022-03-15-twitter-block-advertisers/</guid><description>Requirements For following this Guide you need the following:
a Twitter Developer Account your Twitter Data Archive the programm python3 and pip3 Program Setup Let&amp;rsquo;s start by getting the Program set up.
First, we need to install the requirements by running
pip3 install -r requirements.txt --user After that you need to copy the .env.example file to .env
Now you need to get your Twitter Developer Credential and fill them in the .</description></item><item><title>How to install OpenWrt on the TP-Link Archer C7 V5 in 2022?</title><link>https://nickwasused.com/posts/2022-03-12-tp-link-archer-c7-v5-openwrt/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nickwasused.com/posts/2022-03-12-tp-link-archer-c7-v5-openwrt/</guid><description>The Technical Details Techdata: TP-Link Archer C7 AC1750 v5
(If you don´t want to read all of this in short it means that the Router should have enough power to run current OpenWrt versions.)
The right Firmware Image When installing OpenWrt for the first time you search for a Firmware image that looks like that:
tplink_archer-a7-v5-squashfs-factory.bin
Version 21: https://downloads.openwrt.org/releases/21.02.2/targets/ath79/generic/openwrt-21.02.2-ath79-generic-tplink_archer-a7-v5-squashfs-factory.bin
After you have the right image you need to rename it to:</description></item><item><title>Install Tor Snowflake on the Raspberry PI with DietPi.</title><link>https://nickwasused.com/posts/2022-03-12-tor-snowflake/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 14:24:26 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nickwasused.com/posts/2022-03-12-tor-snowflake/</guid><description>Requirements I use a Raspberry Pi 3b with DietPi 8.2.2, which means we need to use 64Bit Packages. I assume that you do everything in your default home folder of the root user. (That is just essential for the last step, but you will notice what you need to change if you use another folder.)
Install GO Automatic Open the diet pi software installer by typing: dietpi-software.
After that, go to search and search for: go.</description></item><item><title>How to install OpenWrt on the TP-Link Archer C7 V5 in 2021?</title><link>https://nickwasused.com/posts/2021-04-08-tp-link-archer-c7-v5-openwrt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nickwasused.com/posts/2021-04-08-tp-link-archer-c7-v5-openwrt/</guid><description>Disclaimer This guide is a little outdated, you should use OpenWrt version 21. I have created an updated Guide here.
The Technical Details Techdata: TP-Link Archer C7 AC1750 v5
(If you don´t want to read all of this in short it means that the Router should have enough power to run current OpenWrt versions.)
The Problem with the Versions The Archer C7 is supported by two major versions of OpenWrt: Version 18 and 19.</description></item></channel></rss>